talentedge.in 2019-09-03

# Privacy Policy - Talentedge

At Talentedge, we are committed to protecting the privacy of all those who visit our website. For us, your visit is the beginning of our relationship. It is our keenest intent to ensure that you feel confident that the information we collect, and you choose to share, will be treated with care and confidentiality. We want our customers and potential customers to feel comfortable while visiting our Website and contacting us through internet-based media.

When you visit and navigate through our site and communicate with us through it, we will not collect any personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. Any non-public personal information that you may provide via our sites will be used solely for the purpose stated on the page where it is collected. (In some cases and in all cases where required by law or regulation, you will be able to update the information that you provide to us either by sending us an e-mail or, where you have established personal profiles with us, by updating your profile online. Please refer to the specific pages where data is collected for more information. Talentedge will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of its own and its affiliated companies unless (i) expressly authorized by you, (ii) necessary to enable Talentedge’s contractors or agents to perform certain functions for us, or (iii) required or permitted by law. In all cases, the Company will disclose the information consistent with applicable laws and regulations and the Company will require the recipient to protect the information and use it only for the purpose it was provided.

Personal information” means data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number. From time to time, the Company may request personal information from you on the Website in order to respond to your questions or deliver a product or service.

The Company welcomes your comments or questions about the Website and provides e-mail IDs for that purpose. Please note that your e-mail, like most, if not all, non-encrypted Internet e-mail communications, may be accessed and viewed by other internet users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to the Company. For that reason, to protect your privacy, please do not use e-mail to communicate information to the Company that you consider confidential.

The e-mail address you submit to receive information from www.talentedge.in will never be disclosed to any third party unless it’s a subsidiary of Talentedge. All e-mails that you receive will be from the domain name talentege.in

**Automatic Collection of User Submissions or other data:** In some instances, where cookies, chat Google, Google Analytics, Google Adword, Google AdSense Advertising and other technologies are used by Talentedge, Talentedge may collect certain user submissions or any other data automatically when you visit the Website, as well as through emails that we may exchange. The collection of this information allows Talentedge to customize your online experience, improve the performance, usability and effectiveness of the Website and to measure the effectiveness of our marketing activities.

From time to time, Talentedge Website may provide links to other websites, not owned or controlled by the Company, that it thinks might be useful or of interest to you. The Company cannot, however, be responsible for the privacy practices used by other website owners or the content or accuracy of those other websites. Links to various other websites do not constitute or imply endorsement by Talentedge of these websites, any products or services described on these sites, or of any other material contained in them.

Talentedge has adopted and adheres to stringent security standards designed to protect non-public personal information at this Website against accidental or unauthorized access or disclosure. Among the safeguards that Talentedge has developed for this Website are administrative, physical and technical barriers that together form a protective firewall around the information stored at this site. Talentedge takes reasonable steps to help protect and secure your user submissions. However, no data storage or data transmission over the internet, or by other means, can be guaranteed to be secure. Thus, while we strive to protect your personal data, Talentedge cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Therefore, you understand, acknowledge, and agree that you transmit certain personal information to the Website at your own risk. If you have any questions or comments regarding the Talentedge’s website privacy policy, please contact us at the address below.

BHAVESHWAR ARCADE, B WING, 7TH FLOOR,  
Opp Shreyas Cinema, L.B.S. Marg, Ghatkopar  
West Mumbai – 400086

E-mail: info@talentedge.in

BEFORE YOU WRITE, note that we cannot assist you with any type of tax matter. Our office may only address questions about Talentedge privacy policies or concerns you may have regarding how Talentedge uses and collects personal information.

**Copyright Notice**

All text, images, and other materials, thus communicable via digital, print or any other media, on this Website are subject to the copyrights and other intellectual property rights of Talentedge. Ownership of the copyrights in the selection, coordination and arrangement of the materials on this Website rests with the Company. These materials thus shall not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor shall these materials be modified or reposted to other sites.

**Trademark Notice**

All trademarks displayed on this Website are subject to the trademark rights of the Company. Unauthorized use of any trademark displayed on this Website is strictly prohibited.

**Disclaimer**

Any information given by the Company on a specific training program or franchise model or other such information pertaining to our training business is given on as is basis without any warranty or representation of any kind. The Company does not represent or warrant that they are accurate, complete or correct. The fees or other expenses indicated are subject to change without any notice. The Company is also not responsible for any loss or damage resulting from the misuse of your personally identifiable information. Unauthorized medication of any information on this Website shall result in criminal prosecution.

Talentedge may change this Policy from time to time. The Company encourages you to periodically re-read this Policy to see if there have been any changes that may affect you. This statement is not intended to, and does not, create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

It is expressly understood and agreed by you that in the event of any dispute, the Courts in Mumbai, India shall have exclusive jurisdiction.
